As times change, difficult cases increase in number!
تتضاعف القضايا المعقّدة مع مضيّ خط الوقت
Today's stage is a karaoke box!
!مسرح اليوم هو حجرة كاراوكي
Love and farewell songs during Christmas!
!أغاني حُب ووداع أثناء الكريسماس
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
The Karaoke Box Murder Case.
جريمة قتل حجرة الكاراوكي
Why am I stuck with you guys during Christmas?
نحن في موسم الكريسماس، فلمَ أنتما من بجواري بالتحديد؟
That's my line.
هذا كلامي
Say, what's up with Shinichi-kun?
ما وضع شينتشي-كن بالمناسبة؟
He only calls once in a while.
يتّصل بي من فترة لفترة فقط
What's his problem?! Christmas only comes once a year!
!يا للوقح! الكريسماس يحلّ مرّةً في العام فحسب
He's such a conceited mystery geek!
!مهووس التحرّي ذاك مجرّد متغطرس فحسب
That he is.
بالفعل
He's always arrogant, snobbish, and mean...
دائماً مفعم بالثقة ومتعالٍ ولئيم
But maybe that's what I like about him!
لكن لديه جوانب حسنة أيضاً
Ran!
ران
What about you? Are you seeing anyone?
ماذا عنك؟ أيوجد شخص تحبّينه؟
Of course I am. Kimura Tatsuya.
بالطبع، اسمه كيمورا تاتسويا
Tatsuya?
ماذا؟ تاتسويا؟
You know, the guy from Lex, that rock band!
إنّه كيمورا تاتسويا من فرقة الروك "ليكس" الصاعدة
Oh, just some entertainer...
مجرّد مشهور إذاً
Dad got me invited to one of their parties!
حصل لي أبي على دعوة لإحدى حفلاتهم
I get to see Tatsuya in the flesh!
!سأستطيع رؤية تاتسويا مباشرةً
Wanna come?
تريدين القدوم؟
You're going to meet him?!
!ستلتقينهم؟
Her family sure is connected.
كما تتوقّع من ابنة مجموعة سوزوكي
When is it?!
متى نذهب؟
Next Sunday!
الأحد القادم
Count me in!
!سآتي حتماً
You're pretty good!
!أنتما بارعتان
Kimura Tatsuya (21) Vocals
(21)  كيمورا تاتسويا المغنيّ الرئيسي
That's for sure.
بالفعل
Much better than some bands out there.
أفضل من فرقةٍ ما
Tatsuya! You've had too much!
!مهلك يا تاتسويا، شربت الكثير
You know you have a talk show after this!
!أخبرتك أنّ لدينا برنامجاً حوارياً بعد هذا
Shove it, Ugly!
!اخرسي! دعيني وشأني يا قبيحة
Ugly?
قبيحة؟
He's really drunk!
إنّه ثمل جدّاً
Yamada Katsumi (21) Drums
ليس هكذا تخاطبها يا تاتسويا
She's simply doing her job as manager.
تؤدي ماري عملها كمديرة فحسب
Have you been doing your job as our drummer?
بذكرك ذلك، هل كنت تقوم بعملك كطبّالنا؟
And you, Mieko.
وأنتِ كذلك يا مييكو
Shibazaki Mieko (20) Guitar
(20) شيبازوكي مييكو غيتار
What was with you today?!
ما خطبك أدائك اليوم؟
I'm sick of your sucky playing!
!سئمت من عزفك السيّئ
Sorry to keep you waiting.
أعتذر على الإطالة
Been waiting for you, Sumii-san.
كنت بانتظارك يا سومي-سان
I had my manager reserve this for us.
طلبتُ من مديرتنا الحجز في محلّك
Sumii Goh (28) Karaoke Box Manager
(28) سومي غو مالك حجرة الكاراوكي
Thanks! I always appreciate your business!
شكراً، أقدّر زيارتك الدائمة لنا
Sure is sad that a former band leader
من المحزن حقّاً أن يدير قائد فرقة سابق
is stuck running a joint like this...
محلّاً متواضعاً كهذا
Don't make me take this back.
!اصمت
Former band leader?
قائد فرقة سابق؟
Huh? That's--
...ماذا؟ هذه الأغنية
Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer.
الرنّة أحمر الأنف
I requested it.
قمتُ بطلبها
For our manager.
لأجلك يا مديرتنا
Terahara Mari (23) Manager
(23) تيراهارا ماري المديرة
It's perfect for you-- you did believe in Santa
...إنّها مثالية لك بما أنّك آمنتِ بسانتا
until middle school.
حتّى المدرسة الإعدادية
Wouldn't you agree, Ms. Snooty Manager?
ألا توافقينني أيّتها المديرة الجميلة دائمة التظاهر؟
Jerk...
...هذا الوغد
Fine. I'll sing your song.
فهمت، عليّ غناؤها فحسب إذاً
Later, Tatsuya!
أراك لاحقاً يا تاتسويا
Bye!
إلى اللقاء
She's good!
!إنّها بارعة
♪ Rudolph, with your nose so bright, ♪
!تبّاً
What's with that sad look?
ما خطب هذه التعابير الحزينة؟
You wanna sing too, kid?
تريد الغناء أيضاً يا صبيّ؟
No, that's okay!
!كلا، لا داعي
Why's that lady crying?
لمَ تبكي تلك الآنسة بينما تغنّي؟
'Cuz I'm saying goodbye.
لأنّي سأودّع
To her and the band.
أودّعها والفرقة
Are you quitting Lex?!
!هل ستترك ليكس؟
Yeah. I'm leaving when this tour's over.
أجل، سأرحل حالما تنتهي هذه الجولة
Everyone in the band knows.
الجميع في الفرقة على علم
It's good riddance to these crappy bandmates!
سأودّع الطبّال السيّئ وعازفة الغيتار الطفولية والمديرة المغرورة
That's terrible...
...لا-لا يمكن
Hey, that's my song! Who requested it?
!عجباً، إنّها أغنيتي
Tatsuya, it's time to go!
!تاتسويا! إنّه وقت الذهاب
We're going to miss the talk show!
!علينا الإسراع وإلّا سيفوتك البرنامج الحواري
Shut up! I'll sing whenever I want to!
!اخرسي! سأغنّي متى شعرت برغبة في ذلك
Fine. I'll tell the studio we'll be late.
ليس باليد حيلة
Here we go! Bloody Venus!
!ها نحن ذا، كوكب الزُهرة الدامي
Kimura Tatsuya passionately sang
غنّى كيمورا تاتسويا بشغف
his hit song, "Bloody Venus."
"أغنيته الناجحة "كوكب الزُهرة الدامي
Little did anyone know his voice
لكن لم يخطر ببال أحد
would never be heard again.
أنّها آخر مرّة سنسمع غناءه فيها
Except for his killer, that is.
باستثناء قاتله بالطبع
That was awesome!
!مُذهل
How was my song?
كيف كان غنائي؟
It was great!
!رائعاً
Hey, Katsumi.
كاتسومي
Gimme one of them rice balls.
أعطني من كرات الأرز
Think fast.
هاك
Thank you.
شكراً
Are you really quitting Lex?
المعذرة، هل ستترك ليكس حقاً؟
Don't worry, I'm just going solo.
لا تقلقي، سأبدأ مسيرةً فردية فقط
Solo?
مسيرة فردية؟
My new song's already done.
انتهيتُ من أغنيتي الجديدة
His new song's--
...أغنيته الجديدة
Done?
انتهت؟
What's it called?
ما اسمها؟
Its title? It's called--
...اسمها؟ إنّه
What's wrong?!
ما الخطب؟
Get an ambulance!
!الإسعاف! استدعوا الإسعاف بسرعة
Right!
!حسناً
Too late! He's dead!
لا جدوى، إنّه ميت
That smells like cyanide!
هذه رائحة... سيانيد؟
Somebody planned this!
هذه مكيدة أحدهم
But I was watching the whole time!
وأمام أنظاري، من يكون؟
The first suspect was Sumii, the guy who brought the food.
المُشتبه به الأوّل كان المدير سومي الذي جلب الطعام
He and Kimura Tatsuya used to be bandmates.
كان زميلاً في نفس الفرقة مع كيمورا تاتسويا في الماضي
But then Tatsuya went pro and became popular.
لكنّ تاتسويا أصبح وحده محترفاً واكتسب شعبيّة
It looked like a jealousy murder.
بدت كجريمة غيرة
But he was cleared of suspicion when we learned
لكن تمّت تبرئته عندما عرفنا
that everyone had eaten the food.
أنّ الجميع أكلوا من الطعام
Toxins were found on the victim's clothes and microphone,
وُجِدت سموم على ثياب الضحيّة ومكبّر الصوت بعد التحليلات
so he had touched the poison before eating the rice ball.
لذا فقد انتقل له السمّ قبل أكل كرة الأرز
Which means the killer placed poison on the microphone
ما يعني أنّ القاتل وضع السمّ على مكبّر الصوت
which indirectly adhered to him when he grabbed it.
فانتقل ليد الضحيّة عندما أمسك به
That means it was done by the person who sang before him...
من كان يمكنه فعل ذلك هو الشخص الذي غنّى قبله
...you, Shibazaki Mieko-san!
أي أنت يا شيبازاكي مييكو-سان
I hear you sang a farewell song while crying.
سمعتُ أنّك غنيتِ أغنية وداع بينما تبكين
Did something happen between you two?
هل جرى أمرٌ ما بينكما؟
Tatsuya didn't dump me! He turned me down!
!لـ-لم يهجرني تاتسويا! بل رفضني فحسب
Mieko...
...مييكو
When I told him how I felt...
...عندما بحتُ له بمشاعري
Sorry, Mieko. I already like someone.
آسف يا مييكو، لديّ فتاة مُعجب بها سلفاً
She's gone right now,
ذهبت لمكان ما حالياً
but I'm waiting for her to come back.
لكنّي أنتظر عودتها
He said it couldn't work out between us!
!فقال أنّه لا يستطيع مواعدتي
Then to pay him back, you--
...لذا انتقاماً لمشاعرك قمتِ بـ
No! I didn't kill him!
!كلا! لم أقتله
Already likes someone?
فتاة مُعجب بها؟
Inspector. Tatsuya requested the song that she sang!
حضرة المفتّش، كان تاتسويا من طلب الأغنية التي غنّتها مييكو
She had no idea that he would be singing next!
لم تكن تعلم أنّها ستغنّي، أو أنّ تاتسويا سيتبعها
She couldn't have poisoned the microphone!
يستحيل أنّها من سمّمت مكبّر الصوت
That is true...
...بالفعل
Say, who requested his Bloody Venus song?
"أخبروني، من طلب أغنية "كوكب الزُهرة الدامي التي غنّاها تاتسويا-سان؟
Did he always take his jacket off when he sang?
أكان يخلع سترته قبل الغناء دوماً؟
Only at the start of every Bloody Venus.
فقط عند بداية كوكب الزُهرة الدامي
Could it be?!
...أيمكن
Inspector! What part of his clothing had cyanide on it?!
حضرة المفتّش، أين كان السيانيد على ثياب تاتسويا-سان بالضبط؟
His left elbow area, I believe...
...كوعه الأيسر وفقما أظن
On his staff jacket?!
ماذا عن سترة الفرقة؟
No, there was nothing on his jacket.
كلا، لم يكن هناك شيء عليها
That's it! Now I understand
!فهمت
how the killer poisoned Kimura Tatsuya!
!كيف أوصل القاتل السمّ لكيمورا تاتسويا
And that killer is one of those three
والقاتل الذي كان بإمكانه تنفيذ تلك الحيلة
who have the same jacket on!
!هو أحد الثلاثة الذين يرتدون نفس سترته
Hey, guitar lady.
أخبريني يا عازفة الغيتار
The manager and Tatsuya-san were arguing earlier;
كانت المديرة وتاتسويا-سان يتجادلان قبلاً
were they always like that?
أكانا هكذا دوماً؟
Yeah. They argued about everything.
أجل، صحيح. تجادلا في مختلف الأمور
Tatsuya always started it, though.
لكنّ تاتسويا كان البادئ دائماً
She's not as bad as he claimed.
ليست فتاةً سيّئة كما يدّعي تاتسويا
She's smart, serious, and beautiful--
إنّها ذكيّة ومجتهدة وحسناء
but she never caused any trouble.
ولم يشتك أحد منها قطّ
Inspector Megure!
مفتّش ميغوري
What is it?
ماذا هناك؟
We found this in his office locker.
وجدنا هذه في خزانة مكتب كيمورا تاتسويا
I don't see anything useful here...
لا أرى أيّ خيط قد يفيدنا
It's a band picture...
صورة... صورة للفرقة؟
That sure takes me back.
هذا يُشعرني بالحنين
That's from when he and I had a band
هذه من أيام عزفنا معاً في الفرقة
before he went pro.
قبل أن يُصبح محترفاً
But only he and these two are still
الوحيدان المتبقيان في عالم الموسيقى الآن
in the music industry.
هما تاتسويا وهذا الشخص فحسب
He wasn't the only one who left your band?
لم يكن تاتسويا-سان الوحيد الذي ترك فرقتكم؟
Tatsuya hated that person over there.
إنّها تلك المرأة هناك
Said they were the reason he wanted to quit...
أبغضها تاتسويا، قال أنّه لم يكن ليترك الفرقة دونها
But they're not in that picture...
لكنّها ليست في الصورة
She's right here.
انظر، ها هي
She's really changed, though.
مع أنّها تغيّرت كثيراً
Could it be?
...أيمكن
Too much, if you ask me...
كثيراً جدّاً في الواقع
There's writing on the back!
كتابة خلف الصورة؟
Lemme see it again!
!دعني أراها ثانيةً
I see!
فهمت
But what a sad incident this is if it's true...
...لكن إن كان هذا صحيحاً
You know who did it? How?!
!ماذا؟
Uh-huh. Okay. Got it!
!حسناً، حسناً. فهمت
Cancel the investigation! Get everyone back there!
أوقفوا التحقيق! استدعوا كافة !ذوي العلاقة ولنذهب لساحة الجريمة
Yes, sir!
!حاضر
Did something happen?
أحصل أمرٌ ما؟
He's back.
لقد رجع
He?
رجع؟
A detective you know very well.
مُتحرٍّ عظيم تعرفينه جيّداً
Kudo Shinichi.
كودو شينتشي
Shinichi finally came back!
...رجع شينتشي
Shinichi!
!شينتشي
Welcome! Thank you all for coming!
مرحباً يا سادة، شكراً على قدومكم
Shinichi?
شينتشي؟
He must be watching with this camera!
لا بدّ أنّه يشاهد من هذه الكاميرا
Move, Sonoko!
تحرّكي قليلاً يا سونوكو
Where are you, Shinichi?!
!أين أنت يا شينتشي؟
Let's begin unraveling this case.
لنبدأ بفكّ لثام ألغاز هذه القضيّة
Shinichi!
!شينتشي
What's with this song?
ما خطب هذه الأغنية التي نسمعها لفترة؟
It's Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer.
إنّها "الرنّة أحمر الأنف" يا مفتّش ميغوري
They play it everywhere around Christmas time.
أغنية خاصة بالكريسماس تُعزف في أرجاء المدينة مع قدومه
It also stirs up the killer's hatred for the victim.
كما تؤجج كراهية القاتل لتاتسويا-سان أيضاً
In other words, the person who had Tatsuya-san
أي أنّ القاتل هو من طلب تاتسويا-سان
sing this song.
هذه الأغنية له
Yes. Tatsuya-san's killer
...أجل، قاتل تاتسويا-سان
was his manager, Terahara Mari-san!
!هو المديرة تيراهارا ماري-سان! أنت
She killed him?!
المديرة قتلته؟
No way...
...مستحيل
Stop kidding around!
!توقّف عن المزاح
I wasn't even in the room when he died.
كنتُ خارج الغرفة على الهاتف عندما انهار تاتسويا
You could've poisoned him despite your distance,
،كان بمقدورك تسميمه حتّى مع ابتعادك
simply by having him sing this song.
بجعله يغنّي هذه الأغنية فحسب
This was his hit song, "Bloody Venus"!
!هذه أغنيته الناجحة، كوكب الزُهرة الدامي
Could you sing for us, using the mic I've prepared?
هلّا غنيتِ لنا باستعمال مكبّر الصوت الذي حضّرتُه؟
There's no poison on it, of course.
لا سمّ عليه بالطبع
Fine. If that'll make you happy.
لا بأس، طالما سيرضيك هذا
Wait! Why aren't you removing your jacket?
!انتظري رجاءً
He always took his jacket off when he sang this song.
كان تاتسويا-سان يخلع سترته دوماً عند غنائه هذه الأغنية
Isn't that right, everyone?
أليس صحيحاً يا سادة؟
Yeah...
بـ-بلى
From the top...
...إذاً، لنعد الكرّة
Oh, yes.
أجل، لا أنسى
Don't forget the dance.
تذكّري حركات الرقص
Wow! She's good!
!إنّها بارعة
Of course she is.
بالطبع
She used to sing with Tatsuya in my band.
فقد كانت تغنّي رفقة تاتسويا في فرقتي
She did?
المديرة؟
Satisfied?
أرضيت إذاً؟
Yes.
أجل
Now try eating the food I've prepared.
لتأكلي الطعام الذي حضّرتُه إذاً
You mean this?
هذا؟
Just as Tatsuya-san did.
كما فعل تاتسويا-سان
Pick whatever you'd like.
اختاري أيّ ما يحلو لك
Assuming you can, that is.
هذا إذا افترضنا أنه يمكنك ذلك
I'd rather not. I touched him after he collapsed!
سأمتنع
His hands and clothes had poison on them!
كان هناك سمٌّ على يديه وثيابه
I could've gotten some on my hands too!
!يمكن أنّه انتقل ليديّ
Then please check her jacket, Inspector.
إذاً حضرة المفتّش، تفقّد سترتها التي خلعتها رجاءً
Her jacket?
سترتها؟
Same goes for the jacket! I put it on after touching Tatsuya!
!ينطبق الأمر على سترتي! ارتديتُها بعد لمسي تاتسويا
If there is poison on it, that doesn't mean--
...إن كان هناك سمٌّ عليها فلا يعني ذلك
No. It's not poison I'm looking for.
كلا، لا أبحث عن سمّ
A lighter!
قدّاحة؟
Yes.
أجل
That's his missing lighter.
إنّها قدّاحة تاتسويا المفقودة من مسرح الجريمة
In other words, that's not her jacket--
أي أنّ هذه ليست سترتها
she switched hers with Tatsuya-san's to dispose of the evidence!
!بدّلت خاصتها بسترة تاتسويا-سان للتخلّص من الدليل
She wiped poison on the inside of the left elbow
مسحت السمّ بجانب الكوع الأيسر الداخلي لسترة تاتسويا-سان سلفاً
so that some of it would get on his shirt underneath
فعلت ذلك كي ينتقل
when he put the jacket on.
إلى قميصه الداخلي عندما يرتديه
All that remained was to have him sing Bloody Venus.
"كلّ ما تبقّى هو جعله يغنّي "كوكب الزُهرة الدامي
During his dance, he throws the jacket off
كعادته أثناء الرقص، خلع سترته
and touches his hands to his elbows.
ولمس بيده كوعه الأيسر في الغناء فانتقل السمّ
Then he dies of poisoning when he eats afterward.
بعدها سيتسمّم بأكله أيّ طعام بيده تلك
But why would she do that?
لكن لمَ قد تفعل ذلك؟
Her motive is in the photograph on the table.
دافعها موجود في الصورة على الطاولة
It's from when he was in Sumii-san's band.
إنّها من عزفه في فرقة مدير المحلّ في الماضي
What about it?
ما المميّز بها؟
There's no one else in the picture...
لا يوجد غيرهما في الصورة
She is there, Inspector.
إنّها موجودة حضرة المفتّش، هي أيضاً
In the center of the picture, with Tatsuya-san.
في منتصف الصورة مع تاتسويا-سان
Can this be?!
...هـ-هذه
That's right. That picture of her is the very motive
صحيح، هذه الصورة هي دافعها
behind this murder!
!لارتكاب هذه الجريمة
Don't tell me you--
...أيمكن أنّك
That's right! I had plastic surgery!
!صحيح، أجريتُ عملية تجميلية
For Tatsuya!
!لأجل تاتسويا
I fell in love with him back then...
...كنتُ مغرمةً به عندما كنّا في الفرقة
So when he went pro--
...لذا عندما تركها ليصبح محترفاً
Come with me, Mari! You can be my manager!
!تعالي معي يا ماري، يمكنك أن تكوني المديرة
I was so happy when he said that.
كنتُ بغاية السعادة عندما قال ذلك
I thought he felt the same way about me...
...ظننتُ أنّه شاركني مشاعري
So I got the surgery to be worthy of him...
لذا أجريتُ العملية كي أكون امرأةً لائقة به
His attitude suddenly changed after I got it.
تغيّر سلوكه فجأةً بعدها
He would constantly call me ugly.
استمرّ بنعتي بالقبيحة
He even had me sing the Rudolph song earlier!
!جعلني أغنّي الرنّة أحمر الأنف حتّى
That's why he requested the song for you?
أكان ذلك المعنى وراء طلبه الأغنية لك؟
He made me his manager just to insult me!
جعلني مديرةً منذ البداية للسخرية منّي
So he had to pay.
...لذا لم أستطع مسامحته
He had to pay...
!كنتُ أحبّه
...because I loved him!
!فلم أستطع مسامحته
You're wrong, Mari-san.
أخطأتِ يا ماري-سان
Tatsuya-san had been in love with you for quite some time.
لطالما كان تاتسويا-سان يحبّك
Yeah, right! What would you know?!
!لا تسخر منّي! ما الذي تعرفه؟
Mari! He's telling the truth.
ماري! إنّه يقول الحقيقة
Inspector. Can I have that?
حضرة المفتّش، هلّا أعطيتني الصورة؟
This is a love song he wrote about you.
هذه أغنية حبٍّ كتبها عن مشاعره الدائمة لك
I Want to Tell the Real You
أريد أن أخبر ذاتك الحقيقيّة
This is fake!
!هذه مزيّفة
Nope.
ليست كذلك
Those were the lyrics to his newest song.
إنّها كلمات أغنيته الجديدة التي كان سيصدرها
He always talked about you, you know.
لطالما كان يتكلّم عنك
Why's Mari so self-conscious?
لمَ تهتمّ ماري بالمظاهر؟
Why'd she change her face for me?!
!لمَ غيّرت وجهها لي؟
But he always treated me like--
...لكنّه كان يعاملني بازدراء دوماً
He wasn't good at expressing himself...
لم يكن صريحاً بطبعه
I guess he wanted the old you back.
أنا متأكّد أنّه أراد أن تعودي لذاتك السابقة سريعاً
What have I done?!
...ذ-ذلك
Now I see...
فهمت الآن
I'm waiting for her to come back.
لكنّي أنتظر عودتها
Sorry, Mieko. I already like someone.
لذا آسف يا مييكو، لديّ فتاة مُعجب بها
The person he liked was the manager...
كانت المديرة هي من قصدها إذاً
Tatsuya! Tatsuya!
!تاتسويا! تاتسويا
Tatsuya!
!تاتسويا
The combination of a man unable to express his feelings
عجز شاب عن المصارحة بمشاعره
and a woman who hid hers brought forth a sad ending...
قابله فتاة أخفت مشاعرها، فأولدا نهاية حزينة
...in her weeping and tears.
...في دموعها المتساقطة
Only her photograph sadly smiled.
كانت الصورة وحدها مبتسمة بحزن
That's what you get for saying Kudo Shinichi's name...
يا إلهي، هذا ما تجنيه لاستعمالك اسم كودو شينتشي
She's been waiting there three hours
كانت تنتظر لثلاث ساعات بهذا الشكل
for you to come home.
أمام منزلك مترقبةًّ عودتك
I wish I could help, but there's nothing I can do...
أتمنّى لو يمكنني المساعدة، لكن لا حيلة بيدي
Ran...
...ران
Shinichi? Are you in here?
شينتشي؟ أأنت بالداخل؟
Shinichi? Shinichi!
!شينتشي؟ شينتشي
Where are you? Say something if you're there!
!أين أنت؟ أجب إن كنت موجوداً
The lights...
...الأضواء
Shinichi!
!شينتشي
Shinichi?
شينتشي؟
Yeah, it's me.
أجل، إنّه أنا
I'm finally back.
رجعت أخيراً
Shinichi...
...شينتشي
Geez, stop cryin'!
لا تبكي يا حمقاء
Did you wanna see me that badly?
أأردتِ رؤيتي لهذا الحدّ؟
As if!
!من قد يريد؟
I'm glad to see you, Ran.
أنا سعيدٌ برؤيتك
Shinichi...
...شينتشي
Wish you could see yourself right now.
أرى ملامحك الغبيّة
What's that supposed to mean?!
!ما قصدك؟
Well, gotta get goin'.
حسناً، عليّ المغادرة
Still haven't finished that case. Later, Ran!
!فلم أنته من القضيّة التي أعمل عليها، إلى اللقاء يا ران
Wait, Shinichi--
...ا-انتظر، شينتشي
Shinichi!
!شينتشي
"Your Christmas present. Hope you like it! --Shinichi."
.هدية الكريسماس لك، اقبليها بامتنان شينتشي -
Now stop worrying about me, Ran.
كفّي عن القلق بلا داعٍ عليّ الآن يا ران
She's here, Conan-kun!
!لقد أتت يا كونان-كن
...your mom!
!أمّك...
This can't be!
!كلا
Conan Edogawa doesn't have a mom!
!يستحيل أن يملك إيدوغاوا كونان أُمّاً
Professor Agasa--
...بروفسور
Who's that masked guy?!
!من هذا الرجل المقنّع؟
Oh, crap!
!تبّاً
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Conan Edogawa Abduction Case"
قضيّة اختطاف إيدوغاوا كونان
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Knight Baron.
بارون الليل